Adams, Leonard P. Papers /3046
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Poultry farm cases, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Fruit and vegetable farm cases, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Dairy farm cases, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Current and prospective job market conditions for residents of the five-county region. Draft 1965. (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Automation, 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Training, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Report on Economic Trends, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Farm labor report- requests, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Farm Labor Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Farm Labor Project, 1966. Plans, correspondence, reports (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Farm Labor Study, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Bibliography, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Adams, L.P., and Aronson, R.L. Economic trends in N.Y.S., 1959 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Legislative program on Unemployment insurance for N.Y.S. for the 1960's: problems and suggestions for action., 1959 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Address for presentation a the National Convention, American Personnel and Guidance Association, Chicago, Ill., 1962 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- General Correspondence, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- General Correspondence, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Conference- Correspondence, Programs, Summary of Proceedings, 1959-1967 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Joint Legislative Committee on Unemployment Insurance, 1960-1961 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous Publications- Clippings, 1952-1962 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- University of the State of N.Y. 92nd Convocation in Albany, Sept. 21, 1966 Address (Box 24, Folder 11)
- "Items to Read", 1959 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- The Retirement Advisor- Newsletter and Pamphlets, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Utica Study: Weekly Progress Report, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Schedule A- Utica Supplement (Box 25, Folder 2)
- U.S. Department of Labor Publications, 1956-1957 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Correspondence: Utica Project Personnel, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Correspondence: Utica, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Material To Be Filed, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Monthly Job Market Prelim Report, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Budget Material, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Forms- B.L.S. #2488 (Graduates), 1958 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Forms- B.L.S. #2488 (Dropouts), 1958 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Instructions- Schedule "A", 1958 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Instructions- B.L.S. Card #2488, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Revision Card #2488- Utica Schools, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Utica Project Record Book, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Adams-Woolf Bulletin, 1954-1959 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Youth Bulletin Projects, 1954-1958 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Set of Tables for Dr. Adams, 1956-1957 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Utica Study- Paolucci, 1955-1957 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Contract: U.S. Department of Labor & Cornell University, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Schedule "A"- Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- I.B.M Coding Instructions * Cards & A & B, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Outline- Utica Project, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Guidance in the Utica Public Schools, 1948-1958 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Sal Bella, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Thomas Paolucci Travel Month of June, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Ralph Pugliese, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- John Henry, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Robert Bascom, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- William Ross, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Frank Mason, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Krause, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Krawiec, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Similar Studies, 1956-1959 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- N.Y.S.- Department of Labor Publications, 1956-1957 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Personnel For Utica Studies, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 37)
- Miscellaneous, 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Background Materials, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Vadakin- New York Disability Law, 1949-1952 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Interview Letters (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Auburn Study: Gender and Other Variable Factors, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Copies Letters, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Travel Requests, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous, 1950-1951 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Revisions of BLS Employment Statistic Series, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Mimeographed (Copies of what has been done-reference), 1949-1950 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Auburn Study Current Interview File, 1949-1950 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Auburn Study, 1949-1950 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Cross-Section Code (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Auburn Study, Code (Cross-Section) (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Research: International Harvester Project (Auburn), 1950 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Copy 1 Lay-off Code, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Copy 4 Lay-off Code (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Copy 1 Quit Code (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Copy 2 Quit Code (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Auburn Sudy Codes, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Auburn Study Sorting Instructions, 1950-1951 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Sorting Quit Instructions (Box 26, Folder 21)
- I.H. Termination Allowances, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Maps, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Auburn Prulin Reports, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Employment Data- Cayuga County, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Reports, 1944-1945 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Preliminary Report on Study of Job Opportunities for Graduates of Four Year Program, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- "Developing Understanding" Correspondence Folder, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Accreditation, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Memorandums and Correspondence, 1942-1957 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Labor Market in the Buffalo-Niagara Area, 1940-1945 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Labor Market in the Buffalo-Niagara Area, 1940-1943 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- War Manpower Commission Training, 1943-1949 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Plant Studies, 1941-1943 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Replacement Schedule, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Otis Elevator Co., 1941-1943 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Otis Elevator Co. Service Department, 1943-1945 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Occupational Plant Study Fedders Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1942 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Occupational Plant Study Symington-Gould Corporation, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Occupational Plant Study Curtis-Wright Corporation-Airplane Division, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Ledger, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Ledger, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- U.S. Government Material, 1952-1957 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- U.S. Office of Education, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Useful Chronology S.U. Newsletter, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- W.W. Labor-Management Seminar, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Wilhelm Weinberg Labor Management Seminar, 1959-1960 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Travel Requests & Vouchers, 1953-1960 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Rita Zimmerman, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- 5 County Vocational Education Program, 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Survey: Broome, Chenego, Delaware, Otsego, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Leonard P. Adams- Personal, 1949-1963 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Publications, 1949-1951 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  Scope and Contents
  One of the publications is written in French.
- Collective Bargaining Provisions, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Business Research, 1946-1947 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Business Research, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Business Research, 1946-1949 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Labor Management Conference, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- The Problem of Secular Economic Growth In The State of New York, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Report on Institutional Self-Evaluation submitted in connection with Accreditation by the Middle States Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1955-1956 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Supervisory Management, 1947-1948 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Irving Cohen, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Personnel -- Appointments & Service Histories - Anderson, Louise R., 1946-1948 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Leadership And Human Resources At The Places Where People Work, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Labor Market Letters, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Federal Tax For Unemployment Insurance Administration, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Administrative Analysis of Unemployment Insurance, 1943-1946 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- R. Campbell - A.A. Final Report, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Jesse T. Carpenter, 1952-1959 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- C, 1958-1961 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- D, 1958-1960 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- E, 1959-1960 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- F, 1958-1960 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- G, 1958-1961 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- H, 1959-1960 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- I, 1958-1960 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- J, 1958-1960 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- K, 1958-1960 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- L, 1958-1960 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Mc, 1957-1960 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Margaret E. Martin, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- M, 1956-1960 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Correspondence re National Trade Union Centers, 1951-1952 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Nambra, Miss Keiko, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- N, 1957-1960 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- O, 1953-1960 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- P, 1951-1960 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Paterson, John - Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Charles A. Pearce, 1953-1960 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Miss Perkins - Development of Social Legislation in N.Y.S., 1959-1960 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Miss Perkins' Lectures, Spring 1960 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Q, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- R, 1952-1960 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Retirement Advisors, Inc., 1959-1961 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- RAI Advisory Committee, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 28)
- RCI - Advisory Council, 1958-1959 (Box 29, Folder 29)
- Antonio Sagrista, 1959-1960 (Box 29, Folder 30)
- Stephens: Major General re Army, Ind. Manpower, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- S, 1952-1961 (Box 29, Folder 32)
- Sturmthal, 1951-1958 (Box 29, Folder 33)
- T, 1952-1960 (Box 29, Folder 34)
- Mrs. Tracy, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 35)
- Terada, Seiji, 1953-1956 (Box 29, Folder 36)
- U, 1953-1959 (Box 29, Folder 37)
- V, 1953-1960 (Box 29, Folder 38)
- W, 1951-1960 (Box 29, Folder 39)
- A, 1958-1960 (Box 29, Folder 40)
- Aronson, Bob, 1958-1959 (Box 29, Folder 41)
- B, 1958-1960 (Box 29, Folder 42)
- XYZ, 1953-1960 (Box 29, Folder 43)
- Memos to and from the Dean, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 44)
- Memos, Miscellaneous, 1959-1960 (Box 29, Folder 45)
- Correspondence Relating to Anne Woolf, 1956-1957 (Box 29, Folder 46)
- Airlines Study, LPA, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Re: Alcoholics, 1957-1959 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Atomic Developments LPA, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Automation, 1956-1957 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Economic Trends: LPA, 1956-1959 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Education- Financial, 1954-1957 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Education- LPA (General), 1957-1960 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Education- Rehabilitation and Schooling Adolescent Prison Inmates, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Education- Research, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Employment, 1957-1960 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Industry, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- International Labor Organization, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- I.L.A. (International Longshoremen's Association), 1956-1957 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Labor-Industrial LPA, 1956-1957 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Labor - - Political, 1956-1958 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Labor Unions- general, 1956-1958 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Clippings- Miscellaneous LPA, 1956-1959 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- "Social Problems" American Association For Advancement of Science, 1956-1957 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- New York Subway Strike, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- New York Transit System, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Rail Workers (Railroads), 1957 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Schools - Facilities - Program Planning, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Social Security, 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- State Legislature, 1957-1959 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Textile Workers, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Union Research, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- Adams, Leonard P. - Book Reviews, 1950-1957 (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Adams, Leonard P. - Newspaper Clippings, 1957-1959 (Box 30, Folder 28)
- Latin America -- Newspaper Clippings, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 29)
- Labor-Management Relations - General, N.C.1960 (Box 30, Folder 30)
- Adams, Leonard P. - Speeches, 1947-1958 (Box 30, Folder 31)
- Advertisements for the Reprint Series, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 32)
- Adams, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 33)
- Administrative Conference, 1952-1960 (Box 30, Folder 34)
- Administrative Policies & Procedures, 1951-1957 (Box 30, Folder 35)
- Advisory Committee - Selection of Dean, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 36)
- Advisory Council - 1955 forward, 1955-1960 (Box 30, Folder 37)
- Advisory - Until 1954, 1950-1955 (Box 30, Folder 38)
- Alumni (Faculty) Seminar, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 39)
- Alumni Survey, 1955-1956 (Box 30, Folder 40)
- American Arbitration Association, 1951-1956 (Box 30, Folder 41)
- American Association of University Professors, 1952-1953 (Box 30, Folder 42)
- American Economic Association, 1956-1957 (Box 30, Folder 43)
- American Management Association, 1951-1957 (Box 30, Folder 44)
- American Statistical Association, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 45)
- Field Operations Bureau, 1953-1955 (Box 30, Folder 46)
- Foundations, 1959-1960 (Box 30, Folder 47)
- Foundation Information, 1959-1960 (Box 30, Folder 48)
- John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1959-1960 (Box 30, Folder 49)
- Films and Filmstrips, 1955-1960 (Box 30, Folder 50)
- Buffalo Project, 1963-1965 (Box 30, Folder 51)
- Bureau of Employment - NYS, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 52)
- Bureau of National Affairs, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 53)
- Business Conditions in Kalamazoo, 1959-1960 (Box 30, Folder 54)
- Biscuit, Crackers and Pretzels, 1954-1956 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Footwear Industry, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Men's and Boy's Coats and Suits Industry, 1951-1959 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Correspondence - Men's and Boy's Coats and Suits, 1957-1958 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Women's Dress Industry, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Employment Trends in the Candy and Confectionery Industry in New York State, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Industrial Bulletin, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Labor Economics Class, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- International Conference on Industrial Labor Relations, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Report of the Faculty Research Committee on the Administrative Process, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Study of Social Responsibilities of Labor Organizations, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Labor Classroom Materials, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- ILR- 471 Notes, 1957-1959 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Summary Reports on Employment Trends in New York State, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Report on Employment in the New York State Cutlery, Hand Tool and Hardware Industry, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- 3321- Gray Iron Foundries, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- General Committee Material, 1957-1959 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Montgomery County, 1957-1958 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Motor Vehicles Industry, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Optical Instruments and Lenses, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Synthetic Fibers Industry, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Buffalo and Erie County Study Data, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Utica Report, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Labor Management Conference- Suggestions for, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 24)
- Reading- Suggestions for, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 25)
- Bulletin Type Materials and Suggestions, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 26)
- N.Y.S. Employment and Payroll, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 27)
- Industry Data- U.S. and N.Y. (Box 31, Folder 28)
- Construction 1958 and Present Situation, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 29)
- Area Items, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 30)
- Manufacturing Industries in New York State Data (1947-1957), 1958 (Box 31, Folder 31)
- Area Employment Data by Industry- Graphs, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 32)
- mfg Tables, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 33)
- Graphs by Industry (1949-1950; 1953-1954; 1955-1956), 1957 (Box 31, Folder 34)
- Tables- Postal Blanks, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 35)
- Forecasts for 1958 -- General, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 36)
- Industry, Durable, Data for 1958, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 37)
- Industry, Nondurable, Data for 1958, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 38)
- Miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 39)
- Further Research Items -- To Do, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 40)
- Current Periodicals with Statistics, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 41)
- Statistics, Updated to 1957 (Box 31, Folder 42)
- Action Proposals, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 43)
- Unemployment Data, e.g., Dec. Claimants, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 44)
- Youth and the Job Market, 1953-1958 (Box 31, Folder 45)
- Employment Problems, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 46)
- Youth: Employment by Industry: Unemployment, ect 1940-1953, 1954-1956 (Box 31, Folder 47)
- Labor Law Research Project: Some Aspects of Damage Suits Against Unions [Landis & Rosenzweig], 1956 (Box 31, Folder 48)
- Skills in the Labor Force, 1950-1957 (Box 31, Folder 49)
- Dropouts, 1956-1959 (Box 31, Folder 50)
- Powell Study- Ithaca Public Schools- Job Market, 1956-1957 (Box 31, Folder 51)
- A Text on Labor Relations for Use in Vocational High Schools and Other School Use, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 52)
- Workers' Education in Western Europe and the U.S., 1956 (Box 31, Folder 53)
- The National Emergency Provisions of the Taft-Hartley Act: An Analysis, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 54)
- Aviation Employment Problems, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 55)
- Auburn Report Chapter X (Box 31, Folder 56)
- Daniel Alpern Memorial Prize- ILR, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 57)
- Auburn Study- Personnel, 1950-1954 (Box 31, Folder 58)
- Technical Cooperation Between Indonesia and the U.S., 1953 (Box 31, Folder 59)
- Organization and Administration of University Industrial Relations Research, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 60)
- Labor Market Research Committee, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 61)
- Advisory Council, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 62)
- Advisory Council, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 63)
- Advisory Council, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 64)
- ILR Research - Correspondence, 1955-1961 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- ILR Research - Proposal, 1953-1959 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- ILR Research - Spring 1960 Publication Material (Box 32, Folder 3)
- ILR Research - Fall 1959 Publication Material (Box 32, Folder 4)
- ILR Research - Summer 1958 Publication Material (Box 32, Folder 5)
- ILR Research - Fall 1958 Publication Material (Box 32, Folder 6)
- ILR Research - 1957 Publication Material (Box 32, Folder 7)
- ILR Research, Publication Material 1956 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- ILR Research, Publication Material 1955 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- ILR Research, Publication Material 1954 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- R & P Committee Minutes, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- R & P Committee Minutes, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- R & P Committee Minutes, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- R & P Committee Minutes, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- R & P Committee Minutes, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- R & P Committee, 1949-1960 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Research Methods Courses, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- R & P Long Range Proposals, 1959-1960 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Dean's Annual Report - Research Section``, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Application for Public Health Service Research Grant, 1956-1957 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Annual Report, 1959-1960 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Annual Report, 1958-1959 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Annual Report, 1957-1958 (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Annual Report, 1956-1957 (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Annual Report, 1955-1956 (Box 32, Folder 25)
- Annual Report, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 26)
- Annual Report, 1960-1961 (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Labor Management Relations, 1959-1960 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Age Discrimination, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Construction, 1958-1960 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Disability, 1958-1960 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Employment, 1958-1960 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Fringe Benefits, 1958-1959 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Health Insurance, 1958-1960 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- OASI, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Public Assistance, 1958-1959 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Retirement, 1958-1960 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Unemployed, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Unemployment Insurance, 1958-1960 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Workmen's Compensation, 1958-1960 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous (Social Security), 1959 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- State Relief, 1958-1959 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- General Committee Material, 1956-1959 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- A Report for the N.Y.S.J.L.C.O.T.S.E., 1957 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- J.L.C.S.E. - Correspondence - General, 1957-1960 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- J.L.C.S.E. - Newspaper Clippings, 1957-1959 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- J.L.C.S.E. - Informational Material, 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- J.L.C.S.E. - Meeting Minutes, 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- Business Conditions - Forecasts 1959, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- Economic Developments - L.M. Reports, 1956-1957 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Charts - Industry in N.Y.S., 1958 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Employment Service - Role (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Employment Statistics, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- J.L.C.S.E. - Reports, Notes, and Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Non-Agricultural Employment, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 28)
- Small Business Advisory Council, 1957-1959 (Box 33, Folder 29)
- Traveling and Telephone Expenses, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 30)
- Full Employment, 1957-1959 (Box 33, Folder 31)
- Carpet and Rug Industry, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 32)
- Clipping File, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Course Offerings, Fall Term 1960 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Academic Integrity Committee, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Ad Hoc Planning Committee, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Administrative Committee, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Advisory Committee for Broome City Extension, 1954-1959 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Building Committee, 1953-1958 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Committee on Economic Status of the Faculty, 1952-1958 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Committee on Interdepartmental Research, 1956-1957 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Committee on Membership on School Faculty, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Curriculum Committee, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Graduate Committee, 1957-1959 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Graduate Committee, 1952-1959 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Housing Research Center, 1950-1960 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Interdepartmental Committee on Economic Research, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- International Affairs Committee, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Labor Economic Group, 1958-1960 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- NYS Interdepartmental Committee on Low Income, 1957-1959 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Nominations and Elections Committee, 1956-1960 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Scholarship and Awards Committee, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Social Science Research Center, 1956-1959 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Subcommittee on Industrial Migration Problems, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Subcommittee on Low Income Families, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Conferences, 1952-1959 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- University of Minnesota: Conference on Industrial Relations Research 5/17-18/57, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 25)
- Conference on Labor Statistics, July 1955 - Wisconsin (Box 34, Folder 26)
- Economic Development Corporations in NYS, 1953-1954 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- Extension Division, 1946-1960 (Box 34, Folder 28)
- Extension Division: Programs, 1953-1959 (Box 34, Folder 29)
- Extension Division: Proposed Publications, 1957-1958 (Box 34, Folder 30)
- European Productivity Agency Team, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 31)
- European Professors of B.P.A., 1960 (Box 34, Folder 32)
- Adams/Proposed Airline Study -- Field Projects Directory. (Box 36)
  - Adams: Proposed Airline Study, 1956-1957 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Adams Project, 1954-1955 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Adams- Commuting Study, 1954-1956 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Adams: Displaced Workers Ms., 1956-1957 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Adams- After Young People Leave School, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - A & A - Auburn Study, 1954-1956 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Adams- Landsberger Project, 1948-1957 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - American Airlines, 1955-1958 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Aronson-Miller Project, 1951-1957 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Allen Project File, 1962-1964 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Louis Bajan - Advisee, 1963-1965 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Banerjee Project File, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Barron, Milton - Old Age Study, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Bartender's Project, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Bergen Project File, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Bigelow-Sanford Training Program, 1951-1953 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Bloch Project File, 1961-1964 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Blough Project File, 1962-1963 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Blum Bibliography, 1959-1960 (Box 36, Folder 19)